Shen Gu.
เซินกู.
What did you wish for?
คุณปรารถนาอะไร?
My wish...
ความปรารถนาของฉัน...
Where are you going to hang it?
จะเอาไปแขวนที่ไหนคะ?
Don't take my things.
อย่าเอาของของฉันไป
Don't take my jade.
อย่าเอาหยกของฉันไป
That's Mr. Shen's token for Miss Lin.
นั่นคือสัญลักษณ์ของมิสเตอร์เซินสำหรับมิสลิน
It's an heirloom jade of the Shen family.
มันเป็นหยกมรดกสืบทอด ของตระกูลเซิน
Grandfather.
ปู่.
Are you alright, Grandfather?
สบายดีไหมคุณปู่?
Where did you
คุณอยู่ไหน
get it?
เข้าใจไหม?
A collector in Shen City
นักสะสมในเมืองเสิน
invited me to his house.
เชิญฉันไปที่บ้านของเขา
I spotted this jade at once.
ฉันเห็นหยกนี้ทันที
It's broken,
มันพัง
but the owner went to great lengths
แต่เจ้าของก็ทุ่มสุดตัว
to restore it.
เพื่อคืนค่ามัน
You can tell how much it meant to them.
คุณสามารถบอกได้ว่าสิ่งนี้มีความหมายต่อพวกเขามากแค่ไหน
For some reason,
ด้วยเหตุผลบางอย่าง
I just felt a strong connection to it.
ฉันแค่รู้สึกถึงความเชื่อมโยงที่แน่นแฟ้นกับมัน
This jade is my family heirloom.
หยกนี้เป็นมรดกตกทอดของครอบครัวฉัน
Today, I give it to you
วันนี้ยกให้
as a token of my heart.
เป็นสัญลักษณ์แห่งหัวใจของฉัน
It's really meant for you.
มันมีความหมายสำหรับคุณจริงๆ
Grandfather.
ปู่.
If you like it, you can have it.
ถ้าชอบก็สามารถมีได้
Keep it. It'll protect you.
เก็บไว้. มันจะปกป้องคุณ
Alright.
ใช้ได้.
Mr. Xu, the ladder is here.
คุณซู บันไดมาแล้ว
You have to hang the wish yourself for it to count.
คุณต้องแขวนความปรารถนาด้วยตัวเอง เพื่อให้มันนับ
Alright.
ใช้ได้.
Careful.
ระมัดระวัง.
I'll hold it steady for you.
ฉันจะถือมันไว้อย่างมั่นคงเพื่อคุณ
Grandfather.
ปู่.
=Echoes of Gang City=
=เสียงสะท้อนของเมืองแก๊ง=
=Episode 12= (Heart Coming Alive)
=ตอนที่ 12= (หัวใจกลับมามีชีวิต)
It's been a long time since I've been back.
เป็นเวลานานแล้ว ตั้งแต่ฉันกลับมา
Slow down.
ช้าลงหน่อย.
What's wrong?
เกิดอะไรขึ้น?
Nothing.
ไม่มีอะไร.
This building dates back to the Republican era.
อาคารหลังนี้มีอายุย้อนกลับไป สู่ยุครีพับลิกัน
It belonged to someone who once helped Grandfather.
มันเป็นของใครบางคน ที่เคยช่วยเหลือปู่
After a fire
หลังจากเกิดเพลิงไหม้
took their lives,
คร่าชีวิตพวกเขา
Grandfather went through a lot to buy it back
ปู่ผ่านอะไรมามากมาย เพื่อซื้อคืน
and restore it
และกู้คืน
to what it is now.
ถึงสิ่งที่เป็นอยู่ตอนนี้
How is it? Beautiful?
เป็นยังไงบ้าง? สวย?
I'll show you around.
ฉันจะแสดงให้คุณดูรอบ ๆ
Watch your step, Mr. Xu.
ระวังก้าวของคุณนะคุณซู
You brought him to the old family home.
คุณพาเขามา สู่บ้านของครอบครัวเก่า
Looks like you're very satisfied with Shen Gu.
ดูเหมือนคุณจะพอใจมาก กับเสินกู่
Every time I see him,
ทุกครั้งที่เห็นเขา
I feel like
ฉันรู้สึกเหมือน
(As Long As You Are Back) everything was meant to be.
(ตราบใดที่คุณกลับมา) ทุกสิ่งทุกอย่างตั้งใจจะเป็น
Grandfather.
ปู่.
Wanxin,
ว่านซิน
settle Shen Gu in here.
ตั้งถิ่นฐาน Shen Gu ที่นี่
I'm meeting Qingniao Group's president
ฉันมาพบกับประธานของ Qingniao Group
at 2 PM.
เวลา 14.00 น.
That's great.
นั่นเยี่ยมมาก
I wanted to thank him in person.
ฉันอยากจะขอบคุณเขาเป็นการส่วนตัว
I'll go prepare a gift.
ฉันจะไปเตรียมของขวัญ
No need.
ไม่จำเป็น.
I've taken care of it.
ฉันดูแลมันแล้ว
You two just got married. No need to hover around me all day.
คุณสองคนเพิ่งแต่งงานกัน ไม่จำเป็นต้องวนเวียนอยู่รอบตัวฉันทั้งวัน
Go back to your room and rest.
กลับห้องไปพักผ่อน
Changhe, let's go.
ฉางเหอ ไปกันเถอะ
Alright.
ใช้ได้.
Grandfather.
ปู่.
(As Long As You Are Back)
(ตราบใดที่คุณกลับมา)
I'll take you around.
ฉันจะพาคุณไปรอบ ๆ
I just landed here.
ฉันเพิ่งลงมาที่นี่
There are things at the office I need to handle.
มีของอยู่ที่ออฟฟิศ ฉันต้องจัดการ
How about tonight?
แล้วคืนนี้ล่ะ?
It's fine. Work comes first.
ไม่เป็นไร. งานมาก่อน.
Will you be back for dinner?
คุณจะกลับมาทานอาหารเย็นไหม?
Yes.
ใช่.
I'll get going.
ฉันจะไป.
Go on.
ไปต่อ.
Boss,
บอส
back to the office as fast as possible.
กลับถึงออฟฟิศโดยเร็วที่สุด
Don't keep Grandfather waiting.
อย่าให้ปู่รอนาน
Yes.
ใช่.
Hello.
สวัสดี
Welcome to Qingniao Group, Mr. Xu.
ยินดีต้อนรับสู่กลุ่ม Qingniao คุณ Xu
Our chairman has been expecting you.
ประธานของเรารอคุณอยู่
This way, please.
เชิญทางนี้ครับ.
Mr. Changhe, please have a seat here.
นายฉางเหอ กรุณานั่งที่นี่
I didn't expect
ฉันไม่ได้คาดหวัง
Qingniao's president and I
ฉันกับประธานชิงเหนี่ยว
to walk out of the same house just now.
ที่จะเดินออกจากบ้านเดียวกันเมื่อสักครู่นี้
I'm sorry, Grandfather.
ฉันขอโทษคุณปู่
I haven't had the chance
ฉันไม่มีโอกาส
to tell Wanxin yet.
ที่จะบอก Wanxin เลย
Minghui does have a good prospect,
Minghui มีแนวโน้มที่ดี
but it shouldn't have been Qingniao's first choice.
แต่มันก็ไม่ควรจะเป็น ตัวเลือกแรกของชิงเหนี่ยว
If you're the president,
หากคุณเป็นประธานาธิบดี
then it all makes sense.
แล้วทุกอย่างก็สมเหตุสมผล
Not entirely because of Wanxin.
ไม่ใช่เพราะว่านซินทั้งหมด
Her father had already been in contact with us before he passed.
พ่อของเธอได้ติดต่อไปแล้ว กับเราก่อนที่เขาจะจากไป
I've always been the one
ฉันคือคนนั้นเสมอ
handling the cooperation.
การจัดการความร่วมมือ
Why didn't you tell Wanxin
ทำไมไม่บอกหว่านซิน
you're the president?
คุณเป็นประธานาธิบดีเหรอ?
At first, I just wanted to help her through the crisis.
ตอนแรกฉันแค่อยากจะช่วยเธอ ผ่านวิกฤติ
I didn't expect her to propose.
ฉันไม่ได้คาดหวังให้เธอเสนอ
I couldn't refuse.
ฉันปฏิเสธไม่ได้
After that,
หลังจากนั้น
I never found the right moment to tell her.
ฉันไม่เคยพบช่วงเวลาที่เหมาะสม เพื่อบอกเธอ
You should tell her soon.
คุณควรบอกเธอเร็วๆ นี้
Don't let it come between you.
อย่าปล่อยให้มันมาระหว่างคุณ
I understand, Grandfather.
เข้าใจแล้วครับปู่
When you left Gang City,
เมื่อคุณออกจากเมืองกัง
you had nothing.
คุณไม่มีอะไรเลย
You must've suffered a lot
คงจะทรมานมามากแล้ว
to get where you are now.
เพื่อไปยังที่ที่คุณอยู่ตอนนี้
Come and sit.
มานั่งสิ
Tell me everything.
บอกฉันทุกอย่าง
I, Shen Gu, take thee, Xu Wanxin,
ฉัน Shen Gu พาเจ้า Xu Wanxin
to be my lawful wedded wife.
ให้เป็นภรรยาที่ชอบด้วยกฎหมายของฉัน
(Gang City Marriage Registry)
(ทะเบียนสมรสเมืองแก๊งค์)
- I do.
- ฉันทำ.
♪A lonely bench on the street corner♪
♪ม้านั่งโดดเดี่ยวตรงมุมถนน♪
♪Where all feelings come to rest♪
♪ที่ซึ่งความรู้สึกทั้งหมดได้พักผ่อน♪
♪In the night sky, the moon's trail♪
♪บนท้องฟ้ายามค่ำคืน รอยพระจันทร์♪
♪Stitches up and soothes my sorrow♪
♪ปลอบประโลมและบรรเทาความเศร้าโศกของฉัน♪
♪The courage to get close to you♪
♪ความกล้าที่จะเข้าใกล้คุณ♪
♪Drives away my hesitation♪
♪ขจัดความลังเลของฉันออกไป♪
♪Fate turns and brings us together♪
♪โชคชะตาพลิกผันและพาเรามาพบกัน♪
♪I search my memories with all my might♪
♪ฉันค้นหาความทรงจำด้วยสุดกำลังของฉัน♪
♪Love catches me off guard♪
♪ความรักทำให้ฉันไม่ทันระวัง♪
♪You, in the album♪
♪เธอ ในอัลบั้ม♪
♪Shine through my past like starlight♪
♪ส่องอดีตของฉันเหมือนแสงดาว♪
♪You fall between light and shadow♪
♪คุณตกอยู่ระหว่างแสงและเงา♪
♪Melting all my fears away♪
♪ละลายความกลัวทั้งหมดของฉัน♪
♪Those youthful, naive memories are more than enough to heal♪
♪ความทรงจำอันอ่อนเยาว์และไร้เดียงสาเหล่านั้น มากเกินพอที่จะรักษา♪
♪I'm lost in them♪
♪ ฉันหลงไหลในตัวพวกเขาแล้ว ♪
♪The world suddenly has meaning♪
♪จู่ๆ โลกก็มีความหมาย♪
♪Through the pouring rain, I found you♪
♪ท่ามกลางสายฝน ฉันได้พบเธอ♪
♪In the space of our embrace♪
♪ในพื้นที่แห่งอ้อมกอดของเรา♪
♪Stars spill across the sky♪
♪ดาวกระจายไปทั่วท้องฟ้า♪
Grandfather,
คุณปู่
you've just recovered.
คุณเพิ่งฟื้นตัว
Let's head back
กลับกันเถอะ
and rest.
และพักผ่อน
Alright.
ใช้ได้.
Come back to the family house
กลับมาบ้านของครอบครัว
and have dinner together.
และรับประทานอาหารเย็นด้วยกัน
Okay.
ตกลง.
Grandfather.
ปู่.
Sorry to interrupt.
ขออภัยที่ต้องขัดจังหวะ
Nice to meet you, Grandfather.
ยินดีที่ได้รู้จักคุณปู่
Sorry, I need to borrow Shen Gu.
ขออภัย ฉันต้องยืม Shen Gu
We've got a major decision to make.
เรามีเรื่องสำคัญที่ต้องตัดสินใจ
You're the son of the Fang family, right?
คุณเป็นลูกชายของตระกูลฝาง ใช่มั้ย?
Yes.
ใช่.
You're right.
คุณพูดถูก.
I'm Hongsheng.
ฉันชื่อหงเซิง
I'm Qingniao's CFO and legal director.
ฉันเป็น CFO และผู้อำนวยการฝ่ายกฎหมายของ Qingniao
I'm also his partner.
ฉันยังเป็นหุ้นส่วนของเขา
Good.
ดี.
You're following in your dad's footsteps.
คุณกำลังติดตามเข้ามา ตามรอยพ่อของคุณ
But you've got your mom's looks.
แต่คุณมีหน้าตาเหมือนแม่คุณ
My mother is pretty.
แม่ของฉันสวย
So you're saying you're good-looking?
แล้วคุณบอกว่าคุณหน้าตาดีเหรอ?
Very well.
ดีมาก.
It's happy to see by his side.
ดีใจที่ได้เห็นเขาอยู่เคียงข้าง
Please don't say that.
กรุณาอย่าพูดอย่างนั้น.
There are other partners too.
มีพันธมิตรอื่นด้วย
But we started the company together.
แต่เราเริ่มต้นบริษัทด้วยกัน
He can't do without me.
เขาทำไม่ได้หากไม่มีฉัน
Shen Gu is a lucky man.
Shen Gu เป็นคนโชคดี
Grandfather. Mr. Changhe.
ปู่. นายฉางเหอ.
How was it?
มันเป็นอย่างไรบ้าง?
How did the meeting go?
การประชุมเป็นอย่างไรบ้าง?
What do you think
คุณคิดอย่างไร
Qingniao's president is like?
ประธานของชิงเหนี่ยวเป็นอย่างไร?
I've heard he's young,
ฉันได้ยินมาว่าเขายังเด็ก
but he makes rare public appearances.
แต่เขาปรากฏตัวต่อสาธารณะซึ่งหาได้ยาก
Not much is known about him.
ไม่ค่อยมีใครรู้จักเขามากนัก
But to build a company like this,
แต่การจะสร้างบริษัทแบบนี้
he must be exceptional.
เขาต้องเป็นคนพิเศษ
He is young and capable.
เขายังเด็กและมีความสามารถ
He chose to keep investing
เขาเลือกที่จะลงทุนต่อ
and support us publicly
และสนับสนุนเราต่อสาธารณะ
at our lowest point.
ที่จุดต่ำสุดของเรา
He's a man of loyalty.
เขาเป็นคนที่มีความภักดี
Mr. Xu, Wan Xin.
นายซู วันซิน
Today
วันนี้
is a good day.
เป็นวันที่ดี
I've had the kitchen prepare
ฉันเตรียมครัวไว้แล้ว
your favorite dishes.
อาหารจานโปรดของคุณ
Make sure you eat well.
ให้แน่ใจว่าคุณกินดี
Thank you, Mr. Changhe.
ขอบคุณนายฉางเหอ
Changhe,
ฉางเหอ
since I'm already in Shen City...
เนื่องจากฉันอยู่ที่เมือง Shen แล้ว...
Say no more.
อย่าพูดอีกเลย
I know what you want.
ฉันรู้ว่าคุณต้องการอะไร
You could've come yourself.
คุณก็มาเองได้
I wanted to be with her alone.
ฉันอยากจะอยู่กับเธอคนเดียว
She just wouldn't see me.
เธอคงไม่เห็นฉันหรอก
You're not trying hard enough.
คุณไม่ได้พยายามมากพอ
There was also a time when you couldn't get to meet with Xu Wanxin.
มีช่วงเวลาที่คุณไม่สามารถทำได้ พบกับ Xu Wanxin
She's here.
เธออยู่ที่นี่
Long time no see, Miss Su.
ไม่เจอกันนานนะคุณซู
Congratulations, Best Actress Su.
ยินดีด้วย ดารานำหญิงยอดเยี่ยม ซู
Thank you, Lawyer Fang.
ขอบคุณทนายฝาง
No, no. Please come in.
ไม่ ไม่ กรุณาเข้ามา
Please, this way.
เชิญทางนี้ครับ.
What's wrong?
เกิดอะไรขึ้น?
It's so hard to get a meeting with you.
มันยากมากที่จะประชุมกับคุณ
Who's the one who needs help here?
ใครคือคนที่ต้องการความช่วยเหลือที่นี่?
Of course, he's the one asking you.
แน่นอนว่าเขาคือคนที่ถามคุณ
I've got photos of international star Su Mei.
ฉันมีรูปถ่าย ของดาราดังระดับนานาชาติ ซู เหม่ย
Tomorrow's headline is secured.
พาดหัวของวันพรุ่งนี้มีความปลอดภัย
Look.
ดู.
I know you like this.
ฉันรู้ว่าคุณชอบสิ่งนี้
I had it prepared for you.
ฉันเตรียมไว้ให้คุณแล้ว
Grandfather,
คุณปู่
you can eat more, but go easy on the alcohol.
คุณสามารถกินได้มากขึ้น แต่ไปง่ายๆ กับแอลกอฮอล์
You've just recovered. You have to be careful.
คุณเพิ่งฟื้นตัว คุณต้องระมัดระวัง
My granddaughter is so sweet.
หลานสาวของฉันหวานมาก
Have Shen Gu's room at the old family house been arranged?
มีห้องของ Shen Gu ที่บ้านของครอบครัวเก่าจัด?
Yes. The guest room is ready.
ใช่. ห้องรับแขกพร้อมแล้ว
How can a newlywed couple
คู่บ่าวสาวได้ยังไง
sleep separately?
นอนแยกกันเหรอ?
Right. We're married.
ขวา. เราแต่งงานกันแล้ว
I'll accept any condition.
ฉันจะยอมรับเงื่อนไขใดๆ
Consider it my wedding gift to you.
ถือเป็นของขวัญแต่งงานของฉันที่มอบให้คุณ
Thank you.
ขอบคุณ
Where's mine?
ของฉันอยู่ที่ไหน?
Are you married?
คุณแต่งงานหรือยัง
How about
How about
I give you my congratulations?
แล้วไงล่ะ? ฉันขอแสดงความยินดีกับคุณ?
No need.
ไม่จำเป็น.
You guys chat.
พวกคุณคุยกัน..
I'll take off.
ฉันจะออกเดินทาง
Something came up?
มีอะไรเกิดขึ้นเหรอ?
I'm staying at the Xu residence tonight.
คืนนี้ฉันจะพักที่บ้านพักซู
No one asks.
ไม่มีใครถาม
Has he been like this lately?
ช่วงนี้เขาเป็นแบบนี้หรือเปล่า?
It's not even that bad today.
วันนี้ก็ไม่ได้แย่ขนาดนั้น
Usually, he's showing off everywhere.
ปกติเขาจะโชว์ทุกที่
I'm the biggest victim.
ฉันเป็นเหยื่อรายใหญ่ที่สุด
Are you hungry?
คุณหิวไหม?
Let's eat.
มากินกันเถอะ
Let's go.
ไปกันเลย
Take the seat of honor.
ขึ้นนั่งอันทรงเกียรติ
Thank you.
ขอบคุณ
It's nothing.
มันไม่มีอะไร
Here, try this first.
นี่ลองทำดูก่อน
Cheese pumpkin.
ฟักทองชีส
(Xu Wanxin) (How can you tell)
(ซูหว่านซิน) (รู้ได้ไง)
(if someone likes you?)
(ถ้ามีคนชอบคุณ?)
(Xi) (When a guy and a girl)
(สี) (เมื่อชายและหญิง)
(start testing each other.)
(เริ่มทดสอบกันได้เลย)
(Why?)
(ทำไม?)
(Feeling a spark?)
(รู้สึกเป็นประกายเหรอ?)
(Let me guess.)
(ให้ฉันเดานะ)
(It's someone close to you.)
(เป็นคนใกล้ตัว.)
(His name is Shen Gu.)
(ชื่อของเขาคือ Shen Gu)
(Xu Wanxin) (Nice guess.)
(ซูหว่านซิน) (เดาได้ดี)
(Xi: Hey, Wanxin. Are you falling for Shen Gu?)
(Xi: เฮ้ ว่านซิน คุณกำลังตกหลุมรัก Shen Gu หรือเปล่า?)
Hello?
สวัสดี?
You're back?
คุณกลับมาแล้วเหรอ?
I'm downstairs.
ฉันอยู่ชั้นล่าง
Want to grab a late-night bite?
อยากทานอาหารมื้อดึกไหม?
Sure.
แน่นอน.
♪Tonight the rain falls soft and slow♪
♪คืนนี้ฝนโปรยลงมาอย่างช้าๆ♪
♪Blending with letters left unread drifting through the air♪
♪ผสมผสานกับตัวอักษรที่ยังไม่ได้อ่าน ล่องลอยไปในอากาศ♪
♪You turn and look back at me♪
♪เธอหันกลับมามองฉันอีกครั้ง♪
♪In those same eyes familiar tears quietly appear♪
♪ในดวงตาเดียวกันนั้น น้ำตาที่คุ้นเคย ปรากฏตัวอย่างเงียบๆ♪
♪It feels like we have carried so much♪
♪รู้สึกเหมือนแบกอะไรมามากมาย♪
♪So many questions time itself could not make clear♪
♪มีคำถามมากมายเกิดขึ้นเอง ไม่สามารถอธิบายได้ชัดเจน♪
♪The moment you walked into my life♪
♪ช่วงเวลาที่คุณเดินเข้ามาในชีวิตของฉัน♪
♪Every dream I had became something I want with you near♪
♪ทุกความฝันที่ฉันได้กลายเป็นบางสิ่งบางอย่าง ฉันอยากให้เธออยู่ใกล้ๆ♪
♪How many letters have I written just for you?♪
♪ ฉันเขียนจดหมายไปแล้วกี่ฉบับ เพียงเพื่อคุณ?♪
♪If only you could truly hear what my heart is trying to say♪
♪หากเพียงแต่คุณได้ยินอย่างแท้จริง สิ่งที่ใจฉันพยายามจะพูด♪
♪From this life on no distance could keep us apart♪
♪จากชีวิตนี้เป็นต้นไป ไม่มีระยะทางใดที่พรากเราจากกันได้♪
♪The promise we made♪
♪สัญญาที่เราทำไว้♪
♪Will find its way to be fulfilled one day♪
♪จะพบหนทางที่จะเติมเต็ม สักวันหนึ่ง♪
♪But I want more than just that fleeting gaze♪
♪แต่ฉันต้องการมากกว่านี้ มากกว่าการจ้องมองเพียงชั่วครู่นั้น♪
♪Still I have not heard your answer♪
♪ฉันยังไม่ได้ยินคำตอบของคุณเลย♪
♪Can we still rewrite the ending we face?♪
♪เรายังเขียนตอนจบใหม่ได้ไหม เราเผชิญหน้า?♪
♪When regrets begin to turn around you will hear it all♪
♪เมื่อความเสียใจเริ่มหมุนรอบตัวคุณ จะได้ยินมันทั้งหมด♪
♪Everything that leads me back to you♪
♪ทุกสิ่งที่พาฉันกลับไปหาคุณ♪